Guide to the John E. Nance papers, 1960-1990.
Nance, John E. papers
- Series I: Research
  - Tas/Blit/T'boli Genealogies. Genealogy Data IX a to IX h, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Genealogy Data X a to X u, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Genealogy Data XI a, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Genealogy Data XI b, 1988? (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Genealogy Data II, III, IV Tasaday Genealogy Study by Rara and Nab, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Genealogy Data VI, VII, VIII, Tasaday Genealogical Studies by Rara and Nabayra, [after 1989?] (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 1971 to 1988 Tas Genealogical Charts Data V a to V j, 1971-1989 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Vietnam Drafts/Research/Miscellaneous, 1965-1972 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Vietnam Aftermath Notes/Newspapers, 1969-1981 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Vietnam "Sweet Life" series by John Nance, 1955-1982 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Vietnam Associated Press "Ritchie-5 part" series, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - NBC Reports by JN, 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - A Chambers and Misc, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - "Genealogical Method" article by Robert Hackenberg, [after 1972?] (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Dupes. Mostly or all duplicates of earlier pages/data, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Third and Final Footnote on the Tasaday by Zeus Salazar, 1986? (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Genealogy-1989-Rogel-Rara, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Genealogical Data XIV, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Rara Paper for AAA Pub. Gen Data XVIII, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Data File XII Genealogy, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Vietnam Drafts/Articles/Research/Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Photos for Further Studies on the Tasaday, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - AP World Magazine, 1967-1991 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - N. Goldstein, 1974-1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - APN Tasaday RP-AP/Orientation/TV to Russ. Kiriloth?, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 1970's Publications-General, Panamin brochures, further studies, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Smithsonian Institution TAS for AAA, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Lynch-Liaison-IPC Newsletter Report on TS-Fernandez-Lynch-Special Panamin Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Tasaday review clippings (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - "The Land and People of the Philippines" (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Harper and Row, Christian Deschamps (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Journal, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Newspapers, 1980, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Manila (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - The New Yorker, Harper Junior Books group, Time, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Marc Aronson, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Land and People of the Philippines (Box 11, Folder 24-26)
  - Manila (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Tasaday Newspapers and Clippings, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Gallery cards and programs (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Tape transcripts, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Ardus Johnston transcriptions, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - JN-Philippine Stories for AP, 1968-1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - JN-AP Stories from Philippines Faas, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - (by) JN-Philippines AP Stories, 1968-1970 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - JN/AP Nance Stuff, 1960-1971 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Phil-Religion, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Attack on Pope in Philippines, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Pope's Visit to RP 1970 Nov 27-29. Copy and notes, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Benjamin Mendoza/Pope, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Tasaday Newspaper Articles, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Tasaday Articles/Notes, 1971-1995 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Nance Tasaday report drafts, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Tasaday 1st Set and Stories July 8-9, 1971, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Nance, John E '68, 1968-1971 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - AP Stories of August 1971, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - AP Messages Re Tasaday 1971, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Tasaday March 1972 Stories for AP, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - B. Bassett NBC/Tasaday Documentary, 1972-1977 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - AP Friends, letters, story notes, stories and critiques, 1968-1980 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - AP World Tasaday article, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Philippine Sociological Review, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - The World in 1971 by Associated Press, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - PANAMIN tribal report booklets, [after 1975?] (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Government Papers Re Tasaday, 1972-1987 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - 1972 Martial Law Declared by President Marcos, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Audio-Visual/Panamin-Tasaday, 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Fox/Elizalde Report (in Smithsonian) 1971 General Release, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Misc. Outside Requests and Correspondence: Elizalde, JEN, Manila, 1972-1976 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Proposals, Policies, Meetings, Outlines, etc. Panamin 1972-1976, 1966-1975 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Philippine Tribes booklets, 1967-1979 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Notes of Tasaday, 1972-1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Joseph Campbell Materials, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Joseph Chilton Pearce, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - TAS Scholarly Articles, 1971-1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Bible, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Science Magazine, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - U.S. News and World Report, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Magazine Articles and Letters: Science News & Tasaday, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Magazine Articles and Letters: Omni-Tasaday Essay p.41 May 1990, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Magazine Articles and Letters: Breakthrough - Tasaday Story, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Material for Book's Close: Closer for a Part of Book - innocents/injustice compose Tasaday to Susan workers, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Carl Sagan Articles: "Blue Dot and Intelligent Life on Earth": "Primitive" Tribes Fading, 1986-1991 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Carl Sagan Articles: "Blue Dot and Intelligent Life on Earth": Men getting-seeking power equality with women, 1988-1991 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Carl Sagan Articles: "Blue Dot and Intelligent Life on Earth": Meanings of Space Pic from Voyager, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Notes and Ideas on/for Writing the Book: Writing ideas, hints, quotes for Tasaday book, 1983-1988 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Crises in Journalism/Relevant to Re Tasaday: see also Mary Hurst File, 1982-1988 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Readings on the Tasaday: about being a journalist in your own story, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - A Pattern Language for the Tasaday Book - for a writer (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Books re Tasaday and their Controversy and Experiences: Books Catalogue for 1992 AAA/FX Conference, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Books re Tasaday and their Controversy and Experiences: Tasaday Data for File, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Books re Tasaday and their Controversy and Experiences: Notes on Books (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Books re Tasaday and their Controversy and Experiences: The New Yorker Feb.1, 1993, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Books, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Genetic Fingerprinting, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Body Language Actions as Communication, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Speeches, Quotes, Writings with relevance to the Tasaday, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Intellect and science vs. Tasaday, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Deconstructionism and One New Scholarship, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Hoaxes and Fabricated Incidents, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Piltdown Case (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Portland Arts & Lecture Series, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Notes from Lectures, TV, Miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Science & Engineering Lecture Series: Barrows, Davies, Hawking Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Rifkin Jeremy, 1990-1993 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Materials and notes on various lectures and workshops, 1990-1993 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Relevant Magazines and Newspapers (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Earliest JN notes on Tasaday/Elizalde, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - General Tasaday Notes, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Dr. Norton Winters File, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Tasaday Audio Tapes, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Early Tasaday Field Notes Part I, 1971-72 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Early Tasaday Field Notes Part II, 1971-72 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Field Reports of Fernandez/D. Baradas/A. Rogel Kabayo Incident, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - JN Field Notes on Tasaday, 1972-74 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Argosy Magazine to Machlin, 1971-72 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - More Typed Field and Interview Notes Part I, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - More Typed Field and Interview Notes Part II, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Outline, Notes, Drafts (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - JN Notes for The Gentle Tasaday, 1973-74 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Tasaday Pix-Script-Business Correspondence, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - TGT Draft Part I (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - TGT Draft Part II (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - TGT Draft Part III (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Critiques of The Gentle Tasaday m/s, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Arts for Nance Press Kit for HBJ, Inc. (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - J. Gardner, 1975-1980 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - The Gentle Tasaday (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Firearms in the Philippines (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Land and People of the Philippines (Box 14, Folder 23-24)
  - Philippines Yearbook, 1975, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - The Gentle Tasaday (6 copies, 2 the same) (Box 16)
  - Tasaday audiotape transcriptions (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Tasaday transcripts (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Tasaday notes, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - "Tasaday" by Ceres SC Alabado (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - "The Day the Big Bird Came" by Leticia T. Sala (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - The Tasadays 5th grade essay, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Tasaday notes, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
  - Tasaday notes, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Tasaday notes, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
  - Tasaday Files inventory (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Ron Lewis of Portland, Advertising for Tasaday film documentary, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Cultural Survival brochures, notes, 1986-1990 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Readers' Digest Tasaday Story, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Publicity correspondence and mailing list, 1987-1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Columbia Encyclopedia correspondence, notes (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Clippings and articles on tribes, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Bushman, etc. articles, 1983-1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Panamin Statement of Policy for Visiting Remote Communities, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Reservations and Land Laws in Philippines, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Legislation Affecting the Hill tribes and Panamin, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Marlo Morgan: Mutant message, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Health of civilization notes (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Primate Visions notes (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Violence and aggression (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Althea McCoy, Glen May, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Address list (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Alice Hall National Geographic (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Film Garden Entertainment, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Natural History Magazine, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Lost Tribe, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Anthropology publishers (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Articles, clippings (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Drafts, notes on Tribal land law (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Nance payments and expenses, donations, 1970s (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Tasaday travel expenses, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Notes, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Tasaday notes, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Tasaday notes, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Tasaday notes, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Tasaday notes, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Vietnam and Philippine articles, "The Oregonian", 1966-1975 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Postcards (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Tasaday stories, 1971-1988 (Box 17, Folder 34-40)
  - Clippings, Articles (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Transcript: Dula tapes (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Clothing photo, description (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Materials for BBC: overall summary (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Timed translation for Tasaday statements and interviews in Kematu, T'boli, South Catabato, Phils. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Blessen Boone's Testimony (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - English Translation of Tagalog Dula Testimony (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - List of films in the library for BBC (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Walter Cushing Brigade photographs and notes (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Understanding communism drafts, notes, photographs (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Prisons (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - 5 Scandisks, Tasaday photographs (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Magazine, 1930, 1951, 1990-2005 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - News clippings, Tasaday articles, 2000-2005 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Notebooks with clippings (Box 18, Folder 15-16)
  - Notes and articles for Tasaday book (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Thiessen letters and prints (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Lecture fliers and programs (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Messages from the Stone Age (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Talks (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Press releases (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Magazines, 1967-1985 (Box 19, Folder 6-9)
  - Wolf badge (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Nance trip-odds and ends, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Passport photos and headshots (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Two brochures, Salvation army and Firenze information (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Lindbergh trip information, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Captions for color transparencies on the Tasaday People (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Tasaday articles, clippings and correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Captions and descriptions of contact sheets 20-92 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - The Gentle Tasaday original typescript (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Slide/photograph description, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous article clippings, 1967-1990 (Box 19, Folder 20-22)
  - Philippines notebooks (Box 19, Folder 23-24)
  - Magazines, 1960s-1970s (Box 37)
  - Map of Mindanao (Box 39)
  - Map of Mindanao (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Series II: Photographic materials
  Primarily photographs of Tasaday, the Philippines and Vietnam. Includes black and white and color photographs, slides, negatives and contact sheets.
  - Negatives 1, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Negatives 2, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Negatives 3, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Ching's Photos, [N.D.] (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Folder with Color Photo CD, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Tasaday Photo materials Binder 1, 1968-1995 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Tasaday Photo materials Binder 2, 1972-1997 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Tasaday Photo materials Binder 3A, 1972-1987 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Tasaday Photo materials Binder 3B, [after 1970?] (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Tasaday Photo materials Binder 3C, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Tasaday Photo materials Binder 3D, 1972-1989 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Tasaday Photo materials Binder 3E, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Tasaday Photo materials Binder 3F, [1988?] (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Mini Photo Albums, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Negatives and Photos, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Negatives-Tasaday Smithsonian National Geographic Exhibit, [N.D.] (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Tasaday Negatives Folder 1, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - IEA Team (slides), 1972-89 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - JN Vietnam Pix (slides), 1965-68 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Lindbergh in Philippines plus a few Tasaday (slides), 1972-1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Tasaday @ Kemeto and White Plains (also other tribes) 1988 (slides), 1988 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Tasaday @ Kemeto (also Manila) 1988 (slides), 1988 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Unlabeled Slides part I, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Unlabeled Slides part II, 1972-88 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Unlabeled Slides, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Tasaday 1986 (some 1988) (slides), 1986-88 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Tasaday slides and contact sheets, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Tasaday 1987 Pula/Elizalde Manila Part I (slides), 1987 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Tasaday 1987 Pula/Elizalde Manila Part II (slides), 1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Tasaday Manila 1988 (slides), 1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Tasaday, miscellaneous (slides), 1970s, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Philippines Yearbook (slides) (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Tasaday back up set (slides), 1971 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Unlabeled slides, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Tasaday Duplicates (slides) (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Zagreb (slides), 1988 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - "Today's War" slide list and slides (slides) (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - US Forest Service, Artifacts of Time, Four Corners, Tasaday (slides), 1995 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Tasaday (slides), 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Tasaday slides, Album 1, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Tasaday slides, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Tasaday originals (slides), 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Tasaday (slides) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Tasaday (slides) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Tasaday (slides), 1986 (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
  - Tasaday (slides), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Tasaday (slides), 1987 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Tasaday, Vietnam, Nance family slide show (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Tasaday, T'Boli (slides) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Air views, Cebu (slides), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Kematu (slides), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Tasaday in forest (slides), 1989 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Tasaday (slides) (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - T'boy (slides) (Box 20, Folder 13-14)
  - Tasaday (slides), 1989 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Tasaday slides, May visit (slides), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Manila (slides) (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Tasaday visit (slides), 1989 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Unlabeled slides (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Vietnam and Philippine War (slides) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Tasaday (slides), 1988 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Doctors Gen Sen City (slides), 1999 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Mindanao (slides), 1988 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - USFS-Alaska, India (slides), 1997, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - From 4-corners (slides) (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - John's Vietnam Exhibit (slides) (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Canon Beach Sculpture (slides), 1982 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 2nd from aroid (slides), 1994 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Spring (slides), 1995 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Harris Door Rejects (slides), July 1990 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Cantrell RP/VW exhibit (slides), 1991 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Unlabeled (slides), April 1990 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - South Beach Hotel (slides) (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Tasaday Slides I (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Tasaday Slides II (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Tasaday Slides III (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Tasaday Slides IV (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Tasaday Slides V (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Tasaday Slides VI (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Tasaday Slides VII (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Tribal Dupes/Non-Tasaday (slides) (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Slides including Lindbergh (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Tasaday BS 1988 A II115 (slides), 1988 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Taboli/Blut NG's (slides) (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Taboli/Blut NG 6 (slides) (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Taboli 4 (slides) (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Taboli 3 (slides) (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Taboli 2nds or NG New Road (slides) (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - T'Boli/Blit/NGs (slides) (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - T'boli/Blit 2nds NG 70 (slides) (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - T'Boli/Blit/NG (slides) (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Tasaday originals (slides) (Box 21, Folder 33-34)
  - Hurber House (photos and negatives), 1998 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Negatives and contact sheets (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Non-Tasaday contact sheets (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Hanunoo (Negatives, contact sheets) (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Badjaos (negatives) (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Black and white unlabeled photographs (photographs) (Box 21, Folder 40-41)
  - Tasaday cover designs (photographs) (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Tasaday Unpublished Prints (Unused Any Book Tasaday Prints) Part I (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Tasaday Unpublished Prints (Unused Any Book Tasaday Prints) Part II (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Tasaday Unpublished Prints (Unused Any Book Tasaday Prints) Part III (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Tasaday Unpublished Prints (Unused Any Book Tasaday Prints) Part IV (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Tasaday Unpublished Prints (Unused Any Book Tasaday Prints) Part V (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Penns Clemnes Home in PD2; Sally's Oil Deal in Ohio (Photos, contact sheets, and negatives), 2001 May (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Rocky Fork Sleepover/Ohio Photos, contact sheets, and negatives), 2001 May (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - (A) photos (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - (B) Photos and negatives (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - (C) Photos and negatives (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - (D) Photos and negatives (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - (E)Photos and negatives (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - (Unlabeled) Photos and negatives (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - (Unlabeled) Photos and negatives (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - (Unlabeled) Photos and negatives (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - (Unlabeled) Photos and negatives (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Manila T'nalak Exhibit General Scene and City, Air views from Gen San & MLA, 2001 April (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Rize Park Scenes, Good Friday Pageant, Phil National Museum Exhibit, 2001 April (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Unpublished Tasaday Prints I (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Unpublished Tasaday Prints II (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Unpublished Tasaday Prints III (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Unpublished Tasaday Prints IV (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Unpublished Tasaday Prints V (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Tasaday Photographs: Original Prints from Magnum The Gentle Tasaday 1971-72 I, 1971-72 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Tasaday Photographs: Original Prints from Magnum The Gentle Tasaday 1971-72 II, 1971-73 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Tasaday Photographs: Original Prints from Magnum The Gentle Tasaday 1971-72 III, 1971-74 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Tasaday Photographs: Original Prints from Magnum The Gentle Tasaday 1971-72 IV, 1971-75 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Tasaday Photographs: Original Prints from Magnum The Gentle Tasaday 1971-72 V, 1971-76 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Tasaday Photographs: Original Prints from Magnum The Gentle Tasaday 1971-72 VI, 1971-77 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Tasaday Photographs with descriptions, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Contact Sheet & Correspondence (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Vietnam Photos, Negatives, and Contact Sheets (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - LOBO Dupes (photos) (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Tanedo, house (Photos and negatives), 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Tasaday Kemato, Saragani Bay, en route via Jeepnoy (contact sheets, negatives), 1988 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Tasaday (contact sheets, negatives), 1988 (Box 22, Folder 18-19)
  - Tasaday (contact sheets, negatives), 1989 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Tasaday caves (contact sheets, negatives) (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Tasaday (negatives) (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Tasaday (contact sheets, negatives) (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Negatives, print, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Datu Galang with lawyers (contact sheets, negatives), 1988 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Tasaday photographs and press release (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Tasaday photographs at AP NY library (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Tasaday/Philippine (negatives, photographs), 1989 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Photos from the National library and others (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous black and white photographs (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Portrait photographs (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Philippines book photographs (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - RP/MLA (Negatives) (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
  - RP contact sheets (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Agta/Elizalde contact sheets (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - RP/MLA photographs (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Nance and Tasaday, photos, 1993-1999 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - JN pix w/ Tribes in RP including TS, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Hanoi, Vietnam (photos), April 2000 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Hanoi, Vietnam. Perfume Pagoda (photos), 2000 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Hanoi, Vietnam Scenes. Manila Skyline (photos), 2000 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Hanoi, Vietnam: Pottery/Woodcuts, etc. (photos) (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Vietnam, PD Oregon Coast (photos), 2000 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Vietnam, US/PD (photos), 2000 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Saigon/Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam (photos), 2000 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Vietnam: Ca Dai temple (photos), 2000 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous black and white photographs (Box 23, Folder 17-18)